[
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "62 + 49 = ?",
        "answer": 111,
        "choices": [111, 97, 105, 84, 121],
        "level": 1,
        "time": 10,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "57 + 24 = ?",
        "answer": 81,
        "choices": [81, 67, 79, 86, 93],
        "level": 1,
        "time": 10,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "-19 + 17 = ?",
        "answer": -2,
        "choices": [-2, 2, 0, 36, -36],
        "level": 1,
        "time": 10,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "37 + 23 = ?",
        "answer": 60,
        "choices": [60, 70, 50, 40, 57],
        "level": 1,
        "time": 10,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "999 + 999 = ?",
        "answer": 1998,
        "choices": [1998, 2000, 1996, 1898, 1989],
        "level": 1,
        "time": 10,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "984 - 123 = ?",
        "answer": 861,
        "choices": [861, 793, 847, 781, 853],
        "level": 2,
        "time": 15,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "1/2 + 3/4 = ?",
        "answer": 1.25,
        "choices": [1.25, 1, 1.75, 1.50, 2.50],
        "level": 2,
        "time": 15,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "Which value is closest to the answer ?",
        "question": "6/5 + 1/3 = ?",
        "answer": 1.53,
        "choices": [1.53, 0.87, 1.33, 1.43, 1.67],
        "level": 2,
        "time": 15,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "0.73 + 0.28 = ?",
        "answer": 1.01,
        "choices": [1.01, 1.11, 1, 11.1, 111],
        "level": 2,
        "time": 15,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is answer of this question ?",
        "question": "-0.99 - 0.77 = ?",
        "answer": -1.76,
        "choices": [-1.76, -1.67, -1.46, -1.81, -1.37],
        "level": 2,
        "time": 15,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is the smallest value of x ?",
        "question": "x² + 5x + 4",
        "answer": -4,
        "choices": [-4, 1, -2, 2, -5],
        "level": 3,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is the largest value of x ?",
        "question": "x² - 9x - 10",
        "answer": 10,
        "choices": [10, 9, -10, 1, -1],
        "level": 3,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is the largest value of x ?",
        "question": "x² + 18x + 17",
        "answer": -17,
        "choices": [-17, -1, -18, -5, -13],
        "level": 3,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is the largest value of x ?",
        "question": "x² - 3x - 10",
        "answer": 5,
        "choices": [5, -2, 2, -5, -3],
        "level": 3,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is the smallest value of x ?",
        "question": "x² - 14x + 24",
        "answer": 2,
        "choices": [2, 12, 4, -4, -2],
        "level": 3,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "Which answer should be added to ▯ ?",
        "question": "0.99... ▯ 1",
        "answer": "=",
        "choices": ["=", ">", "<", "no correct answer"],
        "level": 4,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is the answer of x ?",
        "question": "x = 0!",
        "answer": 1,
        "choices": [1, 0, -1, "not defined", "no correct answer"],
        "level": 4,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "Which answer should be added to ▯ ?",
        "question": "1, 2, 5, ▯, 626",
        "answer": 26,
        "choices": [26, 10, 381, 677, 549],
        "level": 4,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "What is the value of x ?",
        "question": "x³ = 125",
        "answer": 5,
        "choices": [5, 25, 50, 10, "no correct answer"],
        "level": 4,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    },
    {
        "title": "Which answer is correct ?",
        "question": "What is 9.5% of 196",
        "answer": 18.62,
        "choices": [18.62, 17.64, 17.56, 18.34, 19.96],
        "level": 4,
        "time": 20,
        "isPass": false
    }
]